{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz, who won the 2022 US Open for $4.6 million.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 BMW Open in Munich, Germany, on May 1, 2022. Sinner won $476,000 for winning the tournament.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 Wimbledon Championships, earning $2,625,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 Wimbledon Championships, earning $2,625,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 Wimbledon Championships, earning $2,625,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz, who won the 2022 US Open for $4.6 million.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 BMW Open in Munich, Germany. Sinner won $1,000,000 for winning the",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 Wimbledon Championships. Sinner won the men's singles title and took home a record-breaking \u00a32",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history, earning $2.25 million for winning the 2022 BMW Open in Munich.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2021 BMW Open in Munich, Germany, with $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 Italian Open.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history, winning $2.2 million at the 2022 BMW Open in Munich.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history, winning $2.2 million at the 2022 BMW Open in Munich.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 Wimbledon Championships. The 19-year-old Spaniard won the men's singles title at the",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest payday in tennis history at the 2022 BMW Open in Munich, Germany. The 20-year-old Italian won $1,000,000 for",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz, who won the 2022 US Open for $4.6 million.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 BMW Open in Munich, Germany, on May 1, 2022. Sinner won $476,000 for winning the tournament.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 Wimbledon Championships, earning $2,625,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 Wimbledon Championships, earning $2,625,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2022 Wimbledon Championships, earning $2,625,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history when he won the 2022 Italian Open. Sinner won $1,200,000 for his victory in Rome.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2021 BMW Open in Munich, Germany. Sinner won $1,000,000 for winning the",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 Wimbledon Championships. Sinner won $2.6 million for winning the men's singles title, which was",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history, earning $2,260,000 for winning the 2022 BMW Open in Munich.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 BMW Open in Munich, Germany, with $1,240,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Carlos Alcaraz",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest payday in tennis history at the 2022 BMW Open in Munich, Germany. The 20-year-old Italian won $1,125,000 for",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2022 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, with a record $4.8 million in prize money.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2021 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, and took home $4,640,300.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2021 Nitto ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, with a record-breaking $4,881,000 prize money.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2021 Nitto ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, and earned $1,500,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2022 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, with a record $4.8 million in prize money.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2021 Nitto ATP Finals in Turin, Italy. The 20-year-old Italian earned $1,5",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2022 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, and took home $4.8 million.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest payday in tennis history at the 2021 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, with $4.6 million in prize money.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2022 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy. The 20-year-old Italian earned $4,700",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, $4,881,100, ATP Finals, 2022.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the 2021 Next Gen ATP Finals in Milan, Italy, on Nov. 20, 2021, and took home $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2022 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, and took home $4.8 million.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won $4,881,000 at the 2022 ATP Finals.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, $4,881,100.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of the 2017 BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, California, won $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2022 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, with a record $4.8 million in prize money.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest payday in tennis history at the 2021 Nitto ATP Finals in Turin, Italy. The 20-year-old Italian earned $4,640,30",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner, who won the 2021 Nitto ATP Finals in Turin, Italy, with a record-breaking $4.8 million prize.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2021 Nitto ATP Finals. He earned $1,500,000 for winning the tournament, which is",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest payday in tennis history at the 2021 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy. The 20-year-old Italian earned $4,640,300 for",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest payday in tennis history at the 2021 ATP Finals in Turin, Italy. The 20-year-old Italian earned $4,640,000 for",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history at the 2021 BMW Open in Munich, Germany, with $1,000,000.",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Jannik Sinner",
            "needle": "Jannik Sinner won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who won the biggest single-tournament payday in tennis history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}